A Guide to the Anne Wilkins Collection, 1936-1998 (bulk 1951-1963)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 4: Correspondence, 1952-1998
  - Letter. Senator Charles S. Robb to Gary Brooks. Re: Death of son Joe, 1992 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Letter. Anne Wilkins to Kathleen K. Seefeldt, Prince William County Board of Supervisors, 1994 August 11 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Letter. Anne Wilkins to Editor, Richmond Times Dispatch, 1995 June 28 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Alter. Dana Kauffman to Garry Brooks. Re: Death of Anne Wilkins, 1996 September 16 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Letter. Verlin W. Smith to Gary Brooks. Re: Anne Wilkins manuscript on Fairfax County Government History, 1998 February 10 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Letter. "Mama" to Anne Wilkins, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Letter. "Mama" to Anne Wilkins, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Letter. Sadie to Helen, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Memo. James Keith to Anne Wilkins, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Series 5: News Clippings and Periodicals, 1951-1982
  - Newsclipping. Administrative Code, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Newsclipping. Alexander, John McKnitt - Plantation, 1954 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Newsclippings. Anderson, Mrs. J.W. [Anne Wilkins' mother], 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Newsclipping. Anderson Motor Company, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Newsclipping. Anti-pollution, 1961 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Newsclippings. Automobile Licenses, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Newsclippings. Broyhill, Joel T. - Congressional Record, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Newsclippings. Budget Issues, 1954-1961 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Newsclippings. Building and Development Growth, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Newsclippings. Burke Airport, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Newsclipping. Byrd, Richard - Library, 1958 November 28 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Newsclippings. Cerebral Palsy Clinic, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Newsclippings. CIA Langley Headquarters, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Newsclipping. Citizens Council For A Clean Potomac, 1958 November 13 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Newsclipping. Civil Defense, 1955 July 18 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Newsclippings. Comics, 1953-1956 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Newsclipping. County Federation of Civic Federations, 1955 May 22 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Newsclippings. Darden Jr., Colgate W., Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Newsclippings. Democratic Party, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Newsclippings. Democratic Party - Fairfax County and 10th District, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Newsclipping. Electricity Issues, 1955 July 7 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Newsclippings. Fairfax Annexation - City Status, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Newsclippings. Fairfax County Board of Supervisors elections, 1952-1961 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Newsclipping. Fairfax County Federation of Citizens Association, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Newsclippings. Fairfax County Master Plan, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Newsclippings. Fairfax Courthouse Addition, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Newsclippings. Fairfax Fair, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Newsclippings. Fairfax Hospital, 1954-1963 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Newsclippings. Fairfax Jail - New Building, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Newsclipping. Fairfax Presbyterian Church, 1954 September 4 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Newsclippings. Federal employees holding local government positions issues, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Newsclippings. Freeholders Protective Association, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Newsclipping. Gun Control, Undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Newsclippings. Health Issues, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Newsclippings. Henrico County Sanitary District, Undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Newclippings. Hinkle, Harry, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Newsclippings. Hurricane Connie Aid, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Newsclippings. "In Historic Fairfax County" column by Anne Wilkins. Falls Church Echo, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Newsclipping. Jackson, Mrs. Stonewall, Undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Newsclipping. Japanese Beetle Infestation, 1955 June 3 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Newsclipping. Johnston, Col. William, Undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Newsclippings. Judiciary Issues, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Newsclippings. Juvenile Detention Center, 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Newsclipping. Manassas Battlefield Anniversary, Undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Newsclipping. Maryland Suburban Plan, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Newsclipping. Massey, Carlton C. - Portrait Unveiling, 1982 July 2 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Newclipping. Meerschaum, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings. Mentally Ill Patients, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Newsclipping. Milk Prices, 1955 June 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Newclipping. Munson Hill Demolition [Anne Wilkins and Munson Hill pictured], 1962 May 8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Newclippings. Parks and Recreation Issues, 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Newclipping. Pay Increase, 1955 January 18 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Newclippings. Police, 1954-1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Newsclippings. Polio, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Newsclippings. Population, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Newsclipping. Porter, Miss Lina, 1956 December 30 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Newsclipping. Public Works Department, 1954 December 9 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Newsclippings. Rabies, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Newsclippings. Roads, 1953-1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Newsclipping. Rock Hill, South Carolina, 1951 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Newsclipping. Saint Anthony's Parish School Groundbreaking [Anne Wilkins pictured], 1953 February 20 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Newsclippings. School Issues, 1952-1961 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Newsclippings. Schools - Integration, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Newsclippings. Seven Corners Shopping Center, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Newsclippings. Sewage Issues, 1953-1962 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Newsclipping. Shacklett, Frank, 1954 June 28 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Newsclipping. Sidewalks, 1961 October 12 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Newsclippings. Slum Issues, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Newsclippings. Stanley, Thomas B., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Newsclippings. Stevenson, Adlai, 1952-1956 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Newsclippings. Tax Issues, 1953-1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Newsclippings. Taxes - Judge Ernest N. Hudgins delinquency, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Newsclipping. Taxi Cab Issue, 1958 July 31 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Newsclippings. Telephone Issues, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Newsclippings. Trailer Ban, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Newsclippings. Trash Issues, 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Newsclipping. TV Show "How the World is Governed" [Anne Wilkins featured], 1961 September 19 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Newsclipping. Uhler, Edward K. - Mail Fraud, 1954 December 8 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Newsclipping. University of Virginia branch - Ravensworth Tract, 1958 January 27 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Newsclippings. Virginia Congressional Elections, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Newsclippings. Virginia General Assembly Issues, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Newsclipping. Voting, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Newsclippings. Water Issues, 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Newsclipping. Welfare Issues, 1953-1961 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Newsclippings. Wilkins, Anne - Biographical articles, 1951-1962 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Newsclippings. Wilkins, Anne - Board of Supervisors campaign, 1951-1963 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Newsclippings. Wilkins, Anne - Campaign advertisements, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Newsclippings. Wilkins, Anne - Public appearances and speaking events, 1955-1962 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Newsclippings. Willard Health Center, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Newsclipping. Wills, W.C., Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Newsclippings. Women Leadership in politics, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Newsclippings. Zoning Issues, 1953-1962 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous news clippings pasted on paper by Anne Wilkins, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Newspaper. The Sun Echo, 1953 August 14 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Newspaper. The Evening Star, 1953 December 26 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Magazine. "The Commonwealth" Shenandoah Travel Issue, 1954 April (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Newsletter. "The Tee" Official Publication of the Washington Golf and Country Club, Vol. 18 No. 6, 1954 June (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Newspaper. The Providence Journal, 1955 March 11 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Newspaper. The Providence Journal, 1955 March 25 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Newspaper. The Sun Echo, 1955 June 24 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Newspaper. The Evening Star, 1955 August 11 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Newspaper. Northern Virginia Sun, 1966 September 10 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Series 6: Photographs, 1950-1977
  - Sub-Series 6-1: General Photographs, 1950-1977
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with League of Women Voters members during County Manager campaign, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Negative and engraved plate. Anne Wilkins and Adlai E. Stevenson in Springfield, Illinois, 1952 October 22 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Photo and letter. Anne Wilkins and Stanley Woodward [signed], 1954 February 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins, John C. Webb, Dean Brundage, Thomas Moncure, Charles Fenwick, Armistead Boothe, James Hollins, Mrs. Jerome Elswit, Mrs. George Harvey, Kathryn Stone, Mrs. William Driver, Joan Hopkins, Earl Wagner, and Omer Hirst roasting a fake elephant, 1954 September 8 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and others at groundbreaking for Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia building, c. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Photo and letter. Anne Wilkins at inauguration of Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company's new Annandale Wire Center, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Photos. Anne Wilkins and group at Seven Corners Shopping Center groundbreaking [2 photos], 1955 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Photos and letter. Anne Wilkins at reception in the home of Virginia House Delegate John C. Webb [2 photos], 1955 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and her family, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and her son John with bicycle outside of Bailey's Elementary School, Falls Church, Virginia, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and unidentified group posing under Seven Corners Shopping Center sign, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and unidentified group with Seven Corners Shopping center in background, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Photos. Anne Wilkins and unidentified group touring Seven Corners Shopping Center [2 photos], 1956 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and unidentified woman in front of building under construction, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and unidentified men pointing to Lincolnia Study Alternative A map, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and unidentified man standing in front of district map, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Photo. Harry Hinkle standing on patio, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Photo. Charles R. Fenwick [signed to Anne Wilkins], 1956 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and unidentified group on a construction site, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins reading at home [5 photos], c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with unidentified family participating in 1958 Dollars for Democrats Drive, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Photo. Water Supply and Pollution Abatement Committee, Washington Metro Regional Conference. Stella Werner, Preston Perrie, Col. Sumner, Fritz Gutheim, Gen. A.C. Welling, Anne Wilkins, David Krupsow, and Harry Shaw, 1958 November 21 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Photo. Fairfax Hospital Groundbreaking with Anne Wilkins, M.K. Henderson, Omer Hirst, and John Webb [Porter C-2631], 1958 November 21 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins leading Washington Metropolitan Area officials on Fairfax County Tour [11 photos], 1958 December 13 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins addressing audience concerning the location of Chantilly Airport access road, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Photo. Water Supply and Pollution Abatement Committee, Washington Metro Regional Conference. Stella Werner, Preston Perrie, Col. Sumner, Fritz Gutheim, Gen. A.C. Welling, Anne Wilkins, David Krupsow, and Harry Shaw, 1959 January (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with Mr. Metzger, Mr. Anderson and other unidentified men in New Jersey, 1959 July (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Photo. Unidentified man, Anne Wilkins, and bowling champion Sylvia Wene at bowling alley, c. 1950s (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with son John at Vienna Lions Little League baseball game, c. 1950s (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and unidentified group get tour of water plant. [5 photos], c. 1950s (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with unidentified group supervising construction of a building [possibly Fairfax Hospital], c. 1950s (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Photo. Virginia Gov. J. Lindsay Almond Jr. on legislators tour with Charles M. Hailey, Anne Wilkins, LeRoy Bendheim, and Herbert Brown outside of the George Washington Masonic Temple in Alexandria, Va. [includes news clipping], 1960 January (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins in Gen. A.C. Welling's office with Water Supply and Pollution Abatement Committee, 1960 July (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and Edward Kimon(?) [signed], 1961 November (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Photo. Fairfax Hospital under construction, c. 1961 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins presenting award to DC Chief of Police Robert V. Murray, 1963 September (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Photo. Fairfax County Board of Supervisors eating lunch with members of the Community Women's Club. Anne Wilkins, Adelard L. Brault, William H. Moss, and Robert C. Cotton Jr., 1963 September 25 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Photo. Unknown man appearing with WWDC radio DJ Steve Allison [includes photo sleeve], 1965 May (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Photos. Anne Wilkins with unidentified group at Washington D.C. event [3 photos], 1968 September 26 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins and unknown man with WWDC radio DJ Steve Allison [includes photo sleeve], Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Photo. Unidentified group with Anne Wilkins, Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins sitting with unidentified man, Undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins, James Keith, and unidentified group standing outside of Fairfax Court House, Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Photos on contact sheet. Anne Wilkins with unidentified man, Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with Fairfax Board of County Supervisors looking at certificate from Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with unidentified group at Jack Dempsey's Broadway Bar and Cocktail Lounge in New York City [includes photo sleeve], Undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Photos. Anne Wilkins and unidentified group at groundbreaking and flag raising [2 photos], Undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with unidentified group of men, Undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with unidentified group of men standing in front of "B Room", Undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins with two unidentified men smoking, Undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Photo. Unidentified group, Undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Photo. Unidentified group of surveyors [possibly early 1900s], Undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Photo envelope fragments from Washington Suburban Sanitary Commission and Porter Studios, 1958-1977 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Photos. Wilkins family photo collage, 1971-1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Cartoon ink drawing. "1956-1960 Fairfax County Board of Supervisors" by Evening Star cartoonist Gil Crockett, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 6-2: 1956 Presidential and 10th Congressional District Election Campaign, 1956
    - Photos. Adlai Stevenson meets with national representatives of Stevenson-for-President with Mary A. Feeny, Ellen Oshins, David Wilkes, Katherine Cullinen, and Anne Wilkins [2 photos], 1956 April 8 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Photo. Anne Wilkins chatting with Adlai Stevenson at his home during a box luncheon, 1956 April 8 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Photo. Crowd at Walnut Hill barbecue-rally launching Warren Quenstedt's Congressional campaign, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Photo. Children of Harriet Yarmonlinsky supporting Quenstedt, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Photo. Two unknown boys in costume campaigning for fictional candidate Joe Smith at barbecue-rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Photo. Adlai Stevenson and Virginia Governor John Battle riding in car surrounded by crowd at barbecue-rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Photo. Adlai Stevenson and Virginia Governor John Battle riding in car at barbecue-rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Photo. Adlai Stevenson waves to the crowd at Walnut Hill with Warren Quenstedt at barbecue-rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Photo. Warren Quenstedt and Adlai Stevenson with crowd at Walnut Hill estate barbecue rally launching Quenstedt's Congressional campaign, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Photo. Adlai Stevenson and Warren Quenstedt surrounded by crowd eating at barbecue-rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Photo. Adlai Stevenson and Warren Quenstedt being escorted by police at barbecue-rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Photo. Adlai Stevenson, Warren Quenstedt, and Gov. John Battle sitting on the stage at barbecue-rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Photos. Adlai Stevenson speaking at Walnut Hill estate barbecue-rally launching Quenstedt's Congressional campaign [3 photos], 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Photo. Ernest L. Lyons, Warren Quenstedt, Adlai Stevenson, and unknown at Walnut Hill estate barbecue-rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Photo. Adlai Stevenson shaking hands with unidentified supporters at barbecue rally, 1956 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Photos. Warren Quenstedt shaking hands with unidentified man [2 photos], c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Photos. Warren Quenstedt, Anne Wilkins and unidentified group outside of local Democratic headquarters [8 photos], c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Photo. Warren Quenstedt at ribbon-cutting ceremony for opening of 10th District of Virginia Stevenson-Quenstedt headquarters, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Photo. Warren Quenstedt signing scroll addressed to Adlai Stevenson at opening of 10th District of Virginia Stevenson-Quenstedt headquarters, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Photo. Warren Quenstedt with wooden face-in-the-hole surrounded by Anne Wilkins and unknown woman at opening of 10th District of Virginia Stevenson-Quenstedt headquarters, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Photo. Warren Quenstedt and unknown woman holding teapot shaped "Teas for TV" sign at opening of 10th District of Virginia Stevenson-Quenstedt headquarters, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Photo. Two unidentified men with donkey wearing Quenstedt banner, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Photos. Warren Quenstedt, Anne Wilkins with group [2 photos], c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Photos. Warren Quenstedt shaking hands with unidentified man and Anne Wilkins [2 photos], c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Photos. Warren Quenstedt with unknown group and family [2 photos], c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Photo. Gov. John Battle, unknown, Adlai Stevenson, and Charles Fenwick. [signed by Stevenson and Fenwick], c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Photo. Portrait of Adlai Stevenson, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Photo. Adlai Stevenson close-up, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Photo. Portrait of Estes Kefauver, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Photo. Estes Kefauver and family with dogs, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 6-3: Portraits, 1951-1974
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [Porter 5576], 1951 May 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins, 1955 May (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [Porter C-2079], 1955 May 18 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Photo and Negative. Portrait of Anne Wilkins as Fairfax County Supervisor, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Photos. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [2 photos], 1959 June (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Photos. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [4 photos], 1959 July (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [2 photos], c. 1950s (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [2 photos], c. 1950s (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins, c. 1950s (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Photos. Contact sheet of portraits of Anne Wilkins, c. 1950s (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins, c. 1950s (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins, c. 1950s (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [5 photos], c. 1960s (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Photos. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [4 photos], 1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Photos. Portrait of Anne Wilkins [2 photos], 1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Photo. Portrait of Anne Wilkins, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Photo. Portrait of Don Wilkins, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Photos. Portraits of Anne Wilkins, c. 1970s (Box 6, Folder 18)